But when you see any of these people
who consider themselves conservatives
trying to falsely conflate the violence of white racism
with any other violence,
please point out that there is a very specific sinister-ness
associated with white racist violence.
Black people haven't been killing white people
because they're white.
They have killed them because they were oppressing them
as their slave owners.
They were being violent towards them.
Do you see the difference here?
And that when we talk about white violence,
we are referring to the willingness of white people
to constantly for centuries kill others
solely based on them not being white.
You're damn rude, eh?
...
They might be wearing white people.
I'll be saying,
I'm not sure if you're turning on this on the middle of the way,
because I can scare them off.
But I'm not sure if I'll be占ising them after that.
It's just for some reason for one person.
But I just think they're not going to be using the right
for this person.
There's a lot of people within me.
I can't be lying, but they're not going to be straight from me.
But I'm not going to be saying,
but there's a lot of people who'm on the side of it.
I usually don't care.
I don't care.
But I'm not going to be a good person.
There's a lot of people who're on the side
and the back of it.
I really don't care.